我读到有人发明了一种
Hey, I read that someone invented a way
可以把脚步转换为电磁能量的方法
to covert your footsteps into electromagnetic energy,
这样就能边走路边给手机充电了
so you can charge your cell phone while walking.
这点子我们几年前就想到了
We had that idea years ago.
当初我们怎么没想过去实践呢
How come we never did anything with it?
大概是因为当时我们把设计稿忘在餐厅
Probably because we left the diagram of it in the restaurant,
却没人愿意走回去拿吧
and none of us wanted to walk back.
我知道你在这计划上毫无成果的真正原因
I know the real reason you never made progress with that idea.
你于2007年9月22号想到这个点子
You thought of it September 22, 2007.
两天后  佩妮搬进公寓了
Two days later, Penny moved in,
你全身的血液都灌进了你的小弟弟
and so much blood rushed to your genitals,
于是你的脑子就废了
your brain became a ghost town.
才不是这样呢
That's not what happened.
我记得非常清楚
I remember it distinctly
因为当时我刚创作了一首年度诗歌
because I had just composed my annual poem
美国最著名的儿童教育绘本作家
死于1991年9月24日
以在苏斯博士的逝世纪念日追忆他
commemorating the anniversary of Dr. Seuss's death.
我们不想听
No one wants to hear it.
为何  死去
Why, die.
为何  他会  死去
Why did he die?
人说  老了
Old, told.
人说  他是  老了
I was told he was old.
我不实践那个点子不是因为佩妮
Penny is not the reason I didn't pursue that idea.
是吗  那自从认识她后
Oh, really? Since meeting her,
你最大的成就都有什么
what have been your greatest accomplishments?
很好答
Easy.
跟佩妮上床
Sleeping with Penny.
佩妮甩了他之后  又成功把她拐回来
Getting Penny to go back out with him after she dumped him.
还拐佩妮订了婚
Tricking Penny into getting engaged.
还有几周前  他差点成功做了一个引体向上哦
And a few weeks ago, he almost did a pull-up.
某人貌似该给我磕头认错哦
I think someone owes me an apology.
别难过了
Well, don't feel bad.
我觉得自从我们的生活
I think we've all been distracted
有了女人后  我们都分心了
since the girls entered our lives.
所以你承认艾米让你分心了吗
You admit Amy's a distraction?
太扰乱了
Oh, very much so.
你们评评理  这短信是两天前发的
Listen to this. This is from two days ago.
"你好  希望你今天过得愉快"
"Hi. Hope you're having a good day."
谁有空回她没完没了的调情短信呀
Who has time for this constant sexting?
或许我们的注意力是被分散了
Well, maybe we have lost our focus.
我们聚在一起来场头脑风暴也未尝不可
It wouldn't kill us to get together and brainstorm ideas.
我们可以来一场那种集思会
Ooh, we could have one of those retreats.
就像我们四个人的科学集思会
Like our own science retreat.
我表哥有一间林间小屋
My cousin has a cabin out in the woods.
我不要去林间小屋
I'm not going to a cabin in the woods.
你们没看过《林间小屋》吗
Did you see the movie Cabin in the Woods?
电影讲述5个好朋友来到了密林深处的一座小木屋
可怕的事情接二连三地发生
那我们去酒店好了
Then we'll go to a hotel.
酒店  你们没看过《闪灵》吗
A hotel? Did you see The Shining?
电影讲述一个作家接受了一份酒店冬天看门的工作
当主角一家住进酒店后  诡异的事情接二连三地发生
我们可以去大熊湖
We could go up to Big Bear
找一间湖边小屋
and get a house on the lake.
你们没看过《湖边小屋》吗
Did you see The Lake House?
2006年浪漫戏剧电影
是韩国电影《触不到的恋人》的美国重制版本
《湖边小屋》里没发生恐怖事件啊
Nothing bad happens in The Lake House.
没发生在主角身上  发生在我身上了
Yeah, well, no, not to them. To me.
能穿梭时光的邮箱
Time traveling mailbox.
这部烂片里唯一穿梭的
The only time that traveled
就是我穿梭进粪坑里一个半小时的青春年华
was an hour and half of my life down the toilet.
好吧  那我们就待在这里开会
Fine. Then we'll just stay here and do it.
你怎么不问去不去海滨小屋
Well, you didn't suggest a beach house.
你愿意去吗
You would go to a beach house?
当然不去  你没看过《大白鲨》吗
Well, good Lord, no-- have you seen Jaws?
电影讲述一个海滨小镇出现一头巨大的食人大白鲨
导致多名游客命丧其口
我们四个在讨论
So, the guys and I are talking about
这周末开一个科学集思会
having kind of a science retreat this weekend.
我想询问下你意见
I just wanted to know if that's okay.
因为我们之前说周日要一起吃早午餐
You and I had talked about going to brunch on Sunday...
这周末想去拉斯维加斯吗
Want to go to Vegas this weekend?
当然想
Of course I do.
伯纳黛特
Bernadette?
闺蜜去拉斯维加斯过周末  去吗
Girl's weekend. Vegas. You in?
-当然去  -那就定了
- Hell, yeah! - Yes!
-我去查机票  -我来查酒店
- I'll check flights. - I'll check hotels.
我去检查我的内裤
I'll check my underpants.
我激动到貌似都尿了
I'm so excited, I think I peed.
她们完全没意见
They seem okay with it.
我还以为你不来了呢
I didn't think you'd make it.
何出此言
Why not?
因为你现在有一个稳定的女朋友
Well, 'cause you have a steady girlfriend now,
我们以为你得待在家
and we assumed you'd have to stay home
放食物到你困住她的深坑里
to lower the food down to her in the pit.
跟你报告一下  艾米丽今晚要工作
For your information, Emily is working tonight.
有人会认为她的工作就是要爬出那个深坑
Yeah, one would assume, on getting out of the pit.
好  我们来集中注意力
Okay, let's focus.
女生们都不在  我们有48小时
The girls are gone, we have 48 hours.
无人打扰
There are no distractions.
让我们一起改变世界吧
Let's change the world.
我戴上我的思考小帽了  开始吧
Thinking caps on. Here we go.
真是太令人激动了  我们在创新耶
Ooh, this is exciting. We're innovating.
感觉我们就像《社交网络》里演的那样
I feel like we're in the Facebook movie.
我从未看过那部电影
Oh. I never saw that.
真的假的
Yeah. Really?
那电影超棒的  我发誓我这么说不是因为
It's wonderful, and I swear I'm not saying that
里面有男神贾斯汀·汀布莱克
because Justin Timberlake is in it.
我有蓝光碟
Yeah, I have it on Blu-ray.
我们来看吧
We should watch it.
好啊  我来做爆米花
Cool. I'll make the popcorn.
各位
Guys...
在短短的30秒里  我们从
in 30 seconds, we went from
"一起改变世界"变成了"一起看电视"
"Let's change the world" to "Let's watch TV."
抱歉  你是说"不看"吗
I'm sorry. Is that a "no"?
不了  莱纳德说得对
Okay. No. Leonard's right.
我们是来集思的
We're here to focus.
以前不是有个本子专门记下我们的点子吗
Didn't we used to have a list of all our ideas?
我好像还留着呢
I-I think I still have it.
我没有听到确切的回答
I did not get a clear answer.
所以我先把光盘放下
I'm gonna set this down now.
找到了
Ah, here it is.
我好多年没翻过了
I haven't looked at these in years.
"机器人女友"
"Robot girlfriend."
那是我的点子
Mm, that was mine.
"机器人妓女"
"Robot prostitute."
也是我的
Also mine.
慢着  我不懂
Wait. I'm confused.
既然你有机器人女友了
Why would you need both a robot girlfriend
干嘛还要机器人妓女
and a robot prostitute?
有些"事"是不会拿来摧残自己的机器女友滴
There's just some things you don't do with your robot girlfriend.
天啊  你遇到伯纳黛特后
Boy, when you met Bernadette,
机器人这一领域真是痛失英才啊
the field of robotics really took a hit.
我们先跳过你可以拿来"爽"的所有发明
Okay, let's just skip all the inventions you can have sex with.
找到一个
All right, no-- here we go:
"人体工学加热座垫"
"Ergonomic heated seat cushion."
不  那玩意会"震动"  继续翻
No, it vibrates. Keep going.
算了  我们想一些新点子吧
You know, let's just come up with something new.
很多重要的创新
You know, a number of significant innovations
灵感都来源自科幻小说
have been inspired by science fiction.
地球同步卫星来自亚瑟·克拉克的一篇文章
The-the geosynchronous satellite from Arthur C. Clarke.
英国著名科幻小说家
地球同步卫星轨道被命名为"克拉克轨道"
摩托罗拉的翻盖手机来自《星际迷航》
The Motorola flip phone-- that came from Star Trek.
对啊  我一直怀疑
Yeah, and I've long suspected that the idea
非裔美国人当选总统的点子
of an African-American president was stolen
是剽窃电影《天地大冲撞》
from the movie Deep Impact.
美国1998年的一部科幻灾难电影
片中摩根·弗里曼扮演一名黑人总统
《回到未来2》所说的未来
Hey, the future they show in Back to the Future II
电影讲述80年代的马蒂和博士开时光机到了2015年
帮助解决马蒂儿子的事
离现在只有一年之遥
is only a year away.
那部电影里的很多东西现在仍未被发明呢
A lot of the things in that movie haven't been invented yet.
如果我们可以
How cool would that be
让其中一样变成现实  那该多酷啊
if we could make one of those a reality?
如果我们能找出马蒂的悬浮滑板
If we could figure out the scientific basis
所需的科学依据
for Marty's hover board,
那肯定会得到普遍应用
that would have universal application.
这在绝对零度下是可行的
Well, it's-it's possible at absolute zero,
但我们必须得想办法消除这温度上的限制
but we would have to remove the temperature restrictions.
我有个好点子
Oh, I have an idea.
我猜我的点子跟你的一样
I think I have the same one.
我们得来看《回到过去2》啊
We got to watch Back to the Future II!
我来做爆米花
I'll make the popcorn.
我们先去哪里玩
So, where should we go first?
大厅里有个翻唱乐队
There's a cover band in the lounge.
-不要  -可他们演奏巴瑞·曼尼洛呢
- Nah. - But they play Barry Manilow.
-不去  -可他们名叫"蛮像曼尼洛"呢
- No. - But they're called "Fairly Manilow."
好吧
Oh. Okay.
-太棒了  -不去
- Great! - No!
那你想干什么
Well, what do you want to do?
我们可是在维加斯
Well, we're in Vegas.
我要下楼来"一桶"玛格丽塔酒
I want to go downstairs, get a bucket of margaritas,
肆意热舞  直到狂吐在轮盘赌上
dance until I vomit all over a roulette wheel
再看着呕吐物随轮盘飘洒四方
and watch it go everywhere.
要是我们不想吐怎么办
What if we don't want to vomit?
绝对会吐  所以才会给你"一桶"啊
Oh, you will. That's why they give you the bucket.
怎么了
What?
我老板发来的
It's my boss.
我的实习安排被提前到周一了
They moved my field ride up to Monday.
什么意思
What does that mean?
我本来有一周时间做功课
It means instead of having a week to study,
现在只剩两天了
I only have two days.
太糟糕了
That sucks.
你不能早上再开始看吗
Can you start in the morning?
要看的东西可多着呢
Uh, it's kind of a lot.
我现在先看一点吧
You know, let me do a little tonight,
晚点再来找你们玩
and I'll catch up with you guys later.
-你确定吗  -没事  你们走吧
- You sure? - Yeah, it's okay. Go ahead.
那个  既然佩妮不去了
So, um, now that Penny's not coming...
-我们打死也不会去看"蛮像曼尼洛"  -好吧
- We're not seeing Fairly Manilow. - Okay.
等等  暂停一下
Hold on. Pause.
有点儿不对劲啊  你看
Something doesn't make sense. Look...
2015年  毕夫偷了《体育年鉴》
In 2015, Biff steals the sports almanac
用时光机把它带回1955年
and takes the time machine back to 1955,
交给过去年少的自己
to give it to his younger self.
可他这样做  不就改变了未来吗
But as soon as he does that, he changes the future,
所以他再返回的2015年
so the 2015 he returns to would be
是另一条没有马蒂和博士的2015年时间线
a different 2015, not the 2015 that Marty and Doc were in.
《热浴盆时光机》时我们就讨论过了
This is Hot Tub Time Machine all over again.
电影讲述三个好朋友回到孩提时的滑雪场旅店
利用屋中的热浴盆时光机回到1987年
如果未来的毕夫把年鉴
If future Biff goes back to 2015
交给过去的自己后  马上回到2015年
right after he gives young Biff the almanac,
他就可以回到有马蒂和博士的那个时代
he could get back to the 2015 with Marty and Doc in it.
因为1955年的毕夫要到过21岁生日时
Because it wasn't until his 21st birthday
才下了第一个赌注
that 1955 Biff placed his first bet.
等等  等等
Wait. Whoa, whoa.
这里用"下了"合适吗
Is "placed" right?
什么意思
What do you mean?
当受未来的因素所影响
Is "placed" the right tense
导致一件事有可能在过去的未来发生时
for something that would have happened in the future
用"下了"这个时态合适吗
of a past that was affected by something from the future?
"已经将会下了"吗
Had will have placed?
这才乖嘛
That's my boy.
好了  毕夫直到21岁
Okay, so, it wasn't until his 21st birthday
才已经将会下了第一个赌注
that Biff had will have placed his first bet
赢得了百万美元
and made his millions.
这时他才改变了时间线
That's when he altered the timeline.
没错  但是他已经将会还未下了呀
Yeah, but he had will haven't placed it!
什么
What?!
和《热浴盆时光机》不同
Unlike Hot Tub Time Machine,
这个问题简单多了
this couldn't be more simple.
毕夫把年鉴带去1955年时
When Biff gets the almanac in 1955,
他所创造出的2015年并不是
the alternate future he creates isn't the one
马蒂和布朗博士驾驶时光机
in which Marty and Doc Brown ever use the time machine
所去的2015年
to travel to 2015.
所以
Therefore,
在新的时间线中
in the new timeline,
马蒂和博士从未驾驶着时光机
Marty and Doc never brought the time machine...
等等
W-Wait.
这里用"驾驶着"合适吗
Is "brought" right?
马蒂和博士从未已经会曾经驾驶着吗
Marty and Doc never had have had brought?
我不知道  你刚才故意刁难我的
I don't know. You did it to me.
反正我就这么用了
Oh, I'm going with it.
马蒂和博士从未已经会曾经驾驶着
Marty and Doc never had have had brought
时光机回到2015年
the time machine to 2015.
所以2015年的毕夫也有可能
That means 2015 Biff could also
没有已经有曾经把年鉴带给1955年的毕夫
not had have had brought the almanac to 1955 Biff.
因此  1955年毕夫拿到年鉴的时间线
Therefore, the timeline in which 1955 Biff gets the almanac
恰恰就是
is also the timeline
1955年的毕夫从未拿到年鉴的时间线
in which 1955 Biff never gets the almanac.
不光是"从未拿到"
And not just "never gets."
还是"从未已经拿到  从未曾经拿到
Never have, never hasn't,
从未曾经已经没拿到"
never had have hasn't.
他说得对
He's right.
再说了  谁会取毕夫这种名字啊
Also, what kind of name is Biff?
听着就像当你打开一管品食乐面团的声音
Sounds like when you pop open a can of Pillsbury dough.
哔呋
Biff.
那面团裹在迷你维纳肠上可好吃了
Oh, that stuff is so good wrapped around cocktail weenies.
各位
Guys...
你们知道"维纳肠"这个词
Do you know that the word "Wiener"
是从奥地利首都维也纳的德语写法中来的吗
comes from the German name of the Austrian capital Vienna,
也就是"维纳"
or "Wien"?
你知道奥地利在地图上的形状
Do you know if you look at Austria on a map
和小鸡鸡一模一样吗
it actually looks like a wiener?
各位  我们这是干嘛呢
Guys, what are we doing?
我们把女生们都赶走
W-We sent the girls away
就是为了集中注意力
so we could focus.
我觉得这招不管用
I don't think it worked.
喝完这杯后  也许你会想听曼尼洛
Maybe after this, you'll be in the mood for some Manilow.
喝完这杯  老娘估计就挂了
I think after this, I'll be dead.
看看我们俩在外面玩
Look at us out,
佩妮留在房间学习
while Penny's in the room studying.
我为她骄傲
I'm proud of her.
这是个难得的机会
This is a great opportunity.
她愿意认真对待实在太好了
It's nice to see her take it seriously.
说得对
It is.
不要讨论佩妮了
But enough about Penny.
说说我俩吧
Let's talk about us.
我们俩美翻了
We're looking good.
的确
We are...
不止是美翻了
Better than good.
看看你  凹凸有致都要爆出来了
I mean, look at you. Your body's bangin'!
艾米
Amy!
少来
Don't "Amy" me.
我们老是说佩妮有多火辣
We're always talking about how hot Penny is.
但我们科学家之间要坦诚相待
Come on-- scientist to scientist,
你这对"强子碰撞机"有多大
how big are those Hadron Colliders?
你说得人家好尴尬
You're embarrassing me.
有啥好尴尬的
Oh, don't be embarrassed.
我也可以给你看我脊椎上的凹陷
I'll show you the divot in my spine.
-什么  -没什么大不了的  我生下来就有
- What? - No, no, it's okay. I was born with it.
要是往里面放一节五号电池
If you put a double-A battery in there,
我就会开始踢腿哦
it makes my leg kick.
好了
All right.
一看就感觉比刚才好多了
Oh, this is already better.
没有那么多干扰
There are far fewer distractions in here.
再说  这里本来就是
Plus, this is where our minds
让我们专注于工作的地方
are conditioned to focus on work.
我一直在思考悬浮滑板的问题
So, I've been thinking about the hover boards,
也许能把磁力悬浮技术用在上面
and maybe there's a way we could use maglev technology.
又或者如果能找出过度冷却材料的办法
Or if we could figure out a way to supercool the materials,
我们就能使用量子耦合了
we could utilize quantum coupling.
不知道有人试过这办法没
Well, I wonder if anyone's tried that.
上网查查呗
Go online and look it up.
的确是铁证如山啊
Oh, I can't argue with him.
瞧这屏幕上的形状
It's right there on the screen.
奥地利和鸡鸡长得一模一样
Austria does look like a wiener.
这算什么  老兄
That's nothing, dude.
看看弗罗里达州  那才叫"神雕"
Go check out how hung Florida is.
我相信弗州小姐肯定腿都合不拢了
I'm sure Mrs. Florida's walking funny.
能不能回到正题上来
Can we get back to work?
他说得对
Yeah... he's right.
我还有个想法
Oh, here's a thought.
能不能用一点操作条件反射方法
What if we use some form of operant conditioning techniques
来防止我们偏题
to keep us from getting off topic?
你是说类似行为修正吗
Like behavior modification?
就是那个
Yeah, exactly.
你们知道这些技术
Did you know those techniques
以前是用来教鸽子打乒乓球的吗
were used to actually teach pigeons to play ping-pong?
我才不信呢
That cannot be true.
喂  都打到赛末点了
Hey, it was match point.
有些心理学家
Some psychologists
会加上惩罚来配合操作性条件反射
perform operant conditioning with punishment.
也许我们可以想出一个处罚方式
Maybe we can come up with a punishment
来惩罚偏题行为
for straying off topic.
比如不让看鸽子乒乓球赛的结果吗
Not getting to see who wins at pigeon ping-pong comes to mind.
我们可以每次一有跑题行为
We could snap a rubber band on our wrists
就拿橡皮筋往手腕上弹一下
every time we get sidetracked.
想法不错  要知道在中世纪
Mmm, not bad. You know, in medieval times,
惩罚闲聊行为的装置叫做
idle chatter was punished with a device called
长舌妇的面具[样子像马笼头]
the scold's bridle.
是一个铁笼子
It's an iron cage
套住头锁起来  把舌头刺穿钉住
that's locked around the head and pierces the tongue.
咱要是有一个该有多好
If only we had one.
有了  我可以上亚马逊网找
Oh! I'll check Amazon.
客房服务
Housekeeping!
我们接到投诉
We had a complaint
这里有人把派对气氛全搞没了
about somebody pooping on a party in there!
其实客房小妹就是我们啦
It was us the whole time!
你为什么要告诉她  她本来信了
Why'd you tell her? It was working.
你信了吗
Was it working?
是的
Yeah.
真是对不起
Oh, I'm so sorry.
你们看起来玩得很开心啊
You guys look like you're having fun.
开心死了
We're having the best time.
猜猜谁玩掷骰子赢了一百块
Guess who won $100 playing craps.
这是一块钱
That's a dollar.
那猜猜谁成了给鸡尾酒女侍者高额小费的凯子
Then guess who wildly overtipped a cocktail waitress.
佩妮  我们走吧
Hey, Penny... hey, let's go.
我们发现一个地方有澳大利亚脱衣舞男哦
We found a place that has Australian male strippers.
我们想看看他们是不是反方向转小弟弟
We want to see if they twirl their junk in the other direction.
有种说法  南北半球水平运动的物体
受地转偏向力影响分别向左和向右偏
听起来真不错
That sounds so great.
但我还有一些功课要做
But I have a little more studying to do.
瞧这书呆的德行
Can you believe this nerd?
来嘛  你想坐在这里做书虫
Come on, do you want to sit here being a loser,
还是想看我像袋鼠宝宝一样
or do you want to watch me climb into
勇攀澳大利亚猛男的丁字裤"高峰"
an Australian man's G-string like a baby kangaroo?
姐妹们  我也很想出去玩乐
All right, guys, look, I would love to go out,
但我必须把这些功课做完
but I've got to get this done, okay?
你们在夜店玩得开心点
So have fun at the club.
如果有麻烦  就去找警察叔叔
And if you get in trouble, find a policeman.
如果他脱掉了裤子
And if he's taking off his pants,
那他就不是真正的警察叔叔[舞男]
he is not a real policeman.
好吧  看来这对她来说很重要
Okay, okay, this is obviously very important to her.
我们来帮她  让她快点把功课做完
Let's just, we'll help her study so she can get done quicker.
来吧  我来提问
Here... here, I'm gonna quiz you.
我来提问
I'm gonna quiz you.
笔记在我这里
I got your notes!
如果你想要
If you want these,
就来脱衣舞男俱乐部找吧
they're gonna be at the strip club!
你不去追她吗
Aren't you gonna chase her?
追到衣帽间吗  可以考虑
To the walk-in closet? Sure.
我们都同意了
Okay, so we agree,
无论何时只要有人偏题
whenever someone takes us off topic
粘臂毛的胶带就得被扯掉一块
they get their arm hair yanked off.
我不能让这样的事发生
And I really can't let that happen
否则帮我修眉的女生会以为
or the girl who does my eyebrows will think
我还有别人帮我修毛
I've been cheating on her.
好了  量子耦合的一个好处就是
All right, now, one benefit of quantum coupling...
慢着  问一下
Wait, no, question:
偏不偏题  谁来决定
who decides if someone's gone off topic?
我想很容易判断吧  如果模棱两可就投票决定
I think it'll be pretty clear. If not, we'll take a vote.
还有
Oh, and also...
我们还没有投票呢
W-We didn't vote!
不必投票  你明显是带偏话题了
We didn't have to-- that was clearly a tangent.
快点  继续工作
Now come on. Back to work.
如果我们侧重于量子耦合
If we're leaning towards quantum coupling...
凭什么
Why?
你刚说"量子耦合"
You said "quantum coupling."
让我想起电视剧《量子跳跃》
That made me think of the show Quantum Leap.
这是偏题  是你的错
That's a tangent and it's your fault.
太荒谬了
That's ridiculous.
谢尔顿  我投票这不是带偏题
Sheldon, I vote that is not a tangent.
谢谢  现在我把没帮你撕的补上
Thank you. And now I owe you one.
这全是你的错
That was your fault.
妈呀  好多毛
Ooh, that is a lot of hair.
这下得听珍妮唠叨了
And now I'm gonna hear it from Jenny.
大家住手
Everyone stop.
这是一个愚蠢的主意
This was a stupid idea.
负强化不管用
Negative reinforcement isn't working.
你是说正惩罚[施加负面刺激]吧
I think you mean positive punishment.
负强化是指取消正面刺激[奖励]
Negative reinforcement is the removal of a positive stimulus.
这是个常见的错误
It's a common mistake.
所以这么做真的不是负强化吗
Negative reinforcement is really wrong?
当然  它总是被用错
Oh, it's used incorrectly all the time.
就连比尔·默里
Even Bill Murray makes that mistake
在《捉鬼敢死队》的第一场戏中也错了
in the first scene of Ghostbusters.
不可能  比尔[主演]高大的形像不能毁
No way. Not Bill Murray.
我正在研究超自然能力中
I'm studying the effect of negative reinforcement
负强化的效果
on ESP ability.
比尔·默里高大形象果然毁了
Bill Murray did get it wrong.
跳到棉花糖宝宝那一幕
Jump ahead to the Stay Puft Marshmallow Man.
不要
No!
莱纳德是对的
Leonard's right.
我们不能直接"跳到"
We can't just jump ahead.
-我们得看完整部电影  -听着
- We have to watch the whole movie. - Look.
我们一直在拖延
We keep procrastinating.
我们看了《回到未来2》
We saw Back to the Future II,
鸽子打乒乓球
pigeons playing ping-pong,
一堆形状像男性生殖器的国家
a bunch of countries that look like genitals
还有一个生殖器形状像丹麦的家伙
and one guy whose genitals look like Denmark!
抱歉我点了那个链接
Yeah, sorry for clicking on that.
现在很晚了  我们浪费了几小时的时间
It's late. We've wasted hours.
拜托大家集中精神
Can we please find it in ourselves
今晚出点成果好吗
to do any amount of work tonight?
但我们还没有看到他们捉住一只鬼呢
But we didn't see them bust one ghost.
你是说我们应该在周六的晚上
So y-you're saying we should stand here
站在我的实验室里
in my lab on a Saturday night
用一台破笔记本看完《捉鬼敢死队》吗
and watch the rest of Ghostbusters on a crappy laptop?
不
No.
上啊  敢死队
Go, busters.
结果还真行啊
It really does hold up.
瞧  这比在酒店房间好吧
See? Isn't this better than a hotel room?
是啊  把鸡鸡都甩起来
Yep. Shake that thing!
你见过这么赞的身躯吗
Have you ever seen a body so fine?
我的解剖课上也有些相当热辣的尸体
We had some pretty hot corpses in my anatomy class,
但没有一个能像这样蹦跶
but none of them moved like that!
早上好
Good morning.
要去游泳池吗
You want to go to the pool?
来嘛  你们自己也说过了
Come on... you said it yourself.
只有书呆和书虫才会待在房间里
Only nerds and losers stay in the room.
哇  好亮啊
Wow, it's bright out.
是不是好亮
Isn't it bright?
也许我应该拉上窗帘
I should probably close these curtains.
才怪  拜拜
Nah. Bye!
你去拉上窗帘好吗
Would you please close the drapes?
好的
Okay.